While you're on the phone,we haven't managed to find a few things we need, like extra pillows for the beds and some washing powder.
既然正在跟你通话，我们找不到一些需要的东西，例如床上富余的枕头和洗衣粉。
Is there any here?
这里有吗？
Pillows... yes.If you look in the cupboard, the large white one upstairs to the left of the bathroom door
枕头，是的。如果你去看看楼上浴室门左边的白色大橱柜，
there should be four or five on the top shelf.
在最上层的架子上应该有四、五个。
And if you want to do some washing, there's some powder for that... probably by the back door.
如果你想要洗衣服，洗衣粉可能在后门。
There's a kind of shelf there above the sink.
水槽上面有一个架子。
In fact,I'm sure there's some there,in a large blue box.
事实上，我肯定那里会有，在一个大的蓝盒子里。
You need about half a cup full for each wash.
洗一次你需要大约半勺。
And that reminds me,the spare key to the back door is hanging on a hook on the wall by the sitting room window.
这个提醒我了，后门的备用钥匙挂在客厅窗户旁边的墙上的挂钩上。
Please make sure to put it back when you've used it.
当你使完后请确保将它放回原处。
The previous guests lost it in the garden and I had to get another one made.
之前的客人在花园里把它丢了，我不得不再做一把！
And if you have any trouble with the lamps, you'll find some spare bulbs in a large cardboard box.
如果灯有问题，在大纸盒里有备用灯泡。
It's on top of the washing machine with all kinds of useful things in it.
在洗衣机的上面有各种有用的东西。
Oh,and another thing I forgot to mention when we last spoke... Yes?
我们上次谈话的时候，我还有一件事忘了说了... 什么事？
I've left you a local map,so you'll be able to find your way around easily.
我给你留了一张本地地图，这样你在周边就不会迷路了。
It shows the whole area.
它涵盖了整个地区，
I put it in the top drawer of the chest under the TV in your bedroom.
我把它放在卧室电视机下面，箱子的第一个抽屉里了。
There's a whole file of local information in there too.
里面还有一个当地信息的文件。
Thanks. What about visiting the town?
谢谢。参观城镇怎么样？
Can you give us any advice?
你能给我一些建议吗
Yes.You'll need to take the car.
是的，你需要开车。
It's too far to walk from the flat really.
它离公寓真的很远，没法步行。
You have to pay to leave your car in all the car parks now I'm afraid.
恐怕你把车放在停车场还得交停车费。
I like the one that's by the station best and you can walk to the town centre from there in five minutes.
我最喜欢车站旁边的那个，从那里走到城镇中心要花5分钟。
That's where all the best restaurants are.
那里有所有最好的餐馆，
But if you want a takeaway,the Italian one does really good pasta and pizzas.
但是如果你想打包带走，有一家意大利餐厅做的意大利面和披萨很好吃。
Call 7-3 double 2.8-1 for that one,or 7 double 6,double 1,9for the Chinese.
那家的电话是732281，或者打给中国餐馆766119。
They's both good and they'll both deliver to the flat.
它们都很不错，而且都送外卖到公寓。
As for places to visit, yes, do go and see the railway museum.
至于参观的地方，是的，去看看铁路博物馆吧。
The exhibition is small but really good.
展览很小但是很棒。
It gets very crowded on Sundays, so I suggest you visit it on a quieter day, later in the week, but not on Thursdays which is market day.
周末人很多，所以我建议你在安静的日子里去，每周靠后的几天，但是不要在赶集日，周四去。
you won't find anywhere to park and it's also the only day of the week when they're not open!
你将找不到停车位，而且这是他们一周唯一关门的一天！
Anything else? Not for the moment.Thanks!
还有什么要了解的吗？-暂时没有了，谢谢！